Privacy
=======

This privacy policy sets out how Custom Keto Diet uses and protects any information that you give when you use the website.

Custom Keto Diet is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Custom Keto Diet may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

* Name
* Gender
* Contact information including email address
* Any personal information relevant for dietary purposes (at your discretion)
* Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
* Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

* Internal record keeping.
* We may use the information to improve our products and services.
* We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
* From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. We use cookies for member access to this website.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not.

A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website or potentially result in the loss of function in some areas, member access in particular. For this reason, we recommend that you continue allowing the use of cookies.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Your personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting.

### Third Party Pixels and Cookies

Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we and/or our partners may use pixels and pixel tags, and place, read or use cookies the collect information from your device and/or Internet browser. These cookies do not contain personally identifiable information, however, it may be possible for our third-party business partners to combine it with other information in order to identify your email address or other personally identifiable information about you. For example, the cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, which we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form.

By using our Service, you agree that us and our third-party partners may store, sell, port, combine with other data, monetize, utilize and otherwise use either (i) the personally indefinable information about you that we share with them, or (ii) the personally identifiable information they discover and/or identify as described above. Visitors can also express their choices for display advertising, through the following platforms: Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out platform or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out platform.

We and/or our partners may also use cookies for delivering personalized advertising emails. These cookies are used to identify the visitors of our advertisers’ websites and send personalized emails based on the visitors’ browsing experience. We and/or our partners use cookies, pixels and other tracking technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you, such as your Internet Protocol address and what Web browser you are using, with certain of your online behaviors, such as opening emails or browsing websites. Such information is used to customize ads or content and may be shared with our partners.
